Guide to the University of Chicago Department of Anthropology Records 1929-1997
University of Chicago Library
- Series IX: Finance
  - Subseries 6: Miscellaneous Finance
    - Linguistic Conference, 1994-1995 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Purchase Requests, 1994-1995 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Equipment, 1985-1995 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Equipment, 1983-1995 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Effort Monitoring Reports, 1994-1996 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- Series X: Students
  - Subseries 1: Student Files
    - Anthes, Lois Margaret, 1925 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Sassaman, William M. [1925] (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Martin, Richard A. 1928 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Setzler, Frank M., 1928-1929 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Albert, Owen S.J. 1929-1930 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Hart, Charles W.H. 1930 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Leh, Leonard L. 1929-1930 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Mekeel, Scudder, 1929-1930 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Osgood, Cornelius Berrian, 1929-1930 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Dyk, Walter, 1928, 1931 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Hart, Janet T. 1931 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Commons, Rachel S. 1932 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Grimes, Lena Elwood, 1932 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Hanna, Roscoe Elton Jr. 1932 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Pond, Alonzo W. 1931-1932 [1992] (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Province, John H. 1930-1932 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Stroebel, Charles, 1931-1932 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Winter, William J. 1932 [1992] (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Findlay, Jeannette C. 1928-1933 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Gibson, Ervin D. 1933 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Ketter, Ruth Marie, 1932-1933 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - Kinietz, William V. 1932-1933 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - Maley, Alexander, 1933 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - Mayhall, Mildred P. 1929-1933 (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - Lippincott, William, 1934 (Box 117, Folder 25)
    - Beatty, William C. Jr. 1934 (Box 117, Folder 26)
    - Downey, Fritz K. 1934 (Box 117, Folder 27)
    - Eggan, Frederick Russell, 1934 (Box 117, Folder 28)
    - Elliott, John Bennett, 1933-1934 (Box 117, Folder 29)
    - Glick, Mary Bell, 1934 (Box 117, Folder 30)
    - Horn, Harry A. 1934 (Box 117, Folder 31)
    - Huang, Ku, 1933-1934 (Box 117, Folder 32)
    - Hyatt, Carol Willis, 1932-1934 (Box 117, Folder 33)
    - Mook, Maurice A. 1934 (Box 117, Folder 34)
    - Neitzel, Stuart, 1934 (Box 117, Folder 35)
    - Tax, Sol, 1931-1934 (Box 117, Folder 36)
    - Washington, William E. 1934 (Box 117, Folder 37)
    - Work, June, 1932-1934 (Box 117, Folder 38)
    - Greenlee, Robert Fargo, 1935 (Box 117, Folder 39)
    - Hastings, Russell, 1932-1935 (Box 117, Folder 40)
    - Bram, Joseph N. 1936 (Box 117, Folder 41)
    - Junek, Vladimir, 1935-1936 (Box 117, Folder 42)
    - Schmidt, Helen L. 1935-1936 (Box 117, Folder 43)
    - Spicer, Rosamond B. 1934-1936 (Box 117, Folder 44)
    - Van Ness, William L. 1936 (Box 117, Folder 45)
    - Fast, John E. 1933-1937 (Box 117, Folder 46)
    - Hamilton, Alice E. 1937 (Box 117, Folder 47)
    - Heineman, Rosa A. 1937 (Box 117, Folder 48)
    - Jones, Stella May, 1933-1937 (Box 117, Folder 49)
    - Minus, Marian, 1935-1937 (Box 117, Folder 50)
    - Tucker, Sara Jones, 1934, 1937 (Box 117, Folder 51)
    - Carle, Georgia L. 938 (Box 117, Folder 52)
    - Engberg, Robert M. 1937-1938 (Box 117, Folder 53)
    - Folkner, Mary Jane, 1937-1938 (Box 117, Folder 54)
    - Foster, James Russell, 1938 (Box 117, Folder 55)
    - Gilbert, William H. Jr. 1934-1938 (Box 117, Folder 56)
    - Kasuga, Katsurvo, 1938 (Box 117, Folder 57)
    - Newman, Marshall T. 1933-1935, 1938 (Box 117, Folder 58)
    - Oberg, Kalervo, 1930-1938 (Box 117, Folder 59)
    - Zaun, Donald R. 1937-1938 (Box 117, Folder 60)
    - Berkes, Mediha, 1938-1939 (Box 117, Folder 61)
    - Bunes, Beatrice [Handwritten Addition: Mrs. Robt. Wolfson] 1938-1939 (Box 117, Folder 62)
    - Cutter, Gretchen, 1939 (Box 117, Folder 63)
    - Eggan, Olive, 1939 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Glenn, Nan Ashton, 1939 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Kelly, Katherine M. 1939 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Ruch, Elizabeth, 1937-1939 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Taylor, Zachary, 1932-1938, 1939 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Willis, Roger W. 1939 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Chamberlain, Joseph, 1939-1940 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Halpern, Mary Fuji, 1938-1940 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Haskell, Edward F. 1939-1940 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Hoyne, Susan, 1940 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Kidd, Kenneth E. 1938, 1940 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Wedel, Mildred Mott, 1939-1940 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Damon, Albert, 1941 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Doll, Eugene Edgar, 1938-1941 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Dunlevy, Marion, 1940-1941 (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Embre, John Fee, 1937-1941 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Lepine, Jeanne Ruth, 1939-1941 (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Pannes, Hilgard, 1941 (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Rinaldo, John B., 1939-1941 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Arthur, George [No Degree], 1942 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Brown, Ina Corinne, 1936-1942 (Box 118, Folder 21)
    - Brush, John E. 1942 (Box 118, Folder 22)
    - Cooper, Arch E. 1938-1942 (Box 118, Folder 23)
    - Davis, Allisson, 1940-1942 (Box 118, Folder 24)
    - Nesbit, Paul Flower, 1937-1942 (Box 118, Folder 25)
    - Paul, Benjamin David, 1940-1942 (Box 118, Folder 26)
    - Smith, Harriet M., 1938-1942 (Box 118, Folder 27)
    - Truttman, Virginia, 1942 (Box 118, Folder 28)
    - Darte, Katherine G., 1941-1943 (Box 118, Folder 29)
    - Friedman, Annesta, 1938-1943 (Box 118, Folder 30)
    - Goubaud, Antonio C. 1941-1943 (Box 118, Folder 31)
    - Greenman, Norman, 1943 (Box 118, Folder 32)
    - Hambleton, Elizabeth, 1943 (Box 118, Folder 33)
    - Pardee, Ruth E. 1937, 1943 (Box 118, Folder 34)
    - Reynolds, Earl L. 1939, 1943 (Box 118, Folder 35)
    - Walker, Harry J. 1943 (Box 118, Folder 36)
    - Walker, Rulon A. 1932, 1943 (Box 118, Folder 37)
    - Watkins, Mark Hanna, 1929-1932, 1943 (Box 118, Folder 38)
    - Lee, Edwin F. 1944 (Box 118, Folder 39)
    - Nacao, Phillip, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 40)
    - Nash, Charles H. 1934-1935, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 41)
    - Peirson, Donald, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 42)
    - Sarma, Jyotirmoyee- PhD Problem, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 43)
    - Senter, Donovan, 1940-1944 (Box 118, Folder 44)
    - Thomas, Treva. 1944 (Box 118, Folder 45)
    - Walker, Winslow M. 1940-1944 (Box 118, Folder 46)
    - Wilder, Carleton S. 1937, 1944 (Box 118, Folder 47)
    - Bell, Virginia, 1945 (Box 118, Folder 48)
    - Cruise, Robert B. 1945 (Box 118, Folder 49)
    - Deuel, Thorne, 1939-1945 [1984] (Box 118, Folder 50)
    - Griffin, James B. 1929-1932, 1945 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Hanneman, Emil F. 1944-1945 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Kuramoto, Mary I. 1945 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Lituak, Henry, 1945 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Loeb, Martin B. 1936-1945 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Martin, Roselie, 1944-1945 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Miner, Horace Mitchell, 1936-1945 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Pottenger, Zipporah, 1944-1945 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Richards, Elizabeth A. 1943, 1945 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Sebeok, Thomas A. 1941-1945 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Srole, Leo, 1935-1945 (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Sternberg, Jean Hall, 1944-1945 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Thompson, David E. 1942, 1945 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Wilder, Charles Griggs, 1932-1945 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Wray, Donald E. 1944-1945 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Adams, Robert M. 1941-1946 (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Bennett, John William, 1944-1946 (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Benton, Robert S. 1938-1946 (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Bentzen, Conrad, 1939-1946 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Bentzen, Frances B. 1943-1946 (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Brown, Robert, 1942, 1946 (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - Buitron, Barbara, 1944-1946 (Box 119, Folder 22)
    - De Young, John, 1946 (Box 119, Folder 23)
    - Drake, John Gibb St. Clair [Folder #2], 1946 (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - Dunham, Katherine, 1944-1946 [1982] (Box 119, Folder 25)
    - Field, Amy Walker, 1946 (Box 119, Folder 26)
    - Fuller, Anne M. 1935-1946 (Box 119, Folder 27)
    - Halpern, Abraham Meyer, 1942-1946 (Box 119, Folder 28)
    - Harrington, Jean Carl, 1932-1938, 1946 (Box 119, Folder 29)
    - Hoijer, Harry, 1929-1930, 1945-1946 (Box 119, Folder 30)
    - Kneberg, Madline D. 1937-1946 (Box 119, Folder 31)
    - Lifschultz, Burton B. 1941-1946 (Box 119, Folder 32)
    - Martin, Paul Sidney, 1946 (Box 119, Folder 33)
    - Morgan, Richard G. 1934-1946 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - McGregor, John Charles, 1939-1946 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Macneish, Richard S. 1941-1946 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Peattie, Roderick, 1946 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Quimey, George, I. 1945-1946 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Schaefer, John, 1945-1946 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Senter, Florence Hawley, 1933-1934, 1940, 1945-1946 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Simmons, John. 1946 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Slotkin, James Sydney, 1940-1946 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Smith, Hale G. 1942-1946 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Strauss, Bella, 1944-1946 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Weckler, Joseph Edwin Jr. 1935-1938, 1945-1946 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Wheeler, Hugh, 1946 (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Young, Ernest F. 1946 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Alegria, Ricardo E. 1944-1947 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Barker, George Carpenter, 1945-1947 (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Bleiler, Everett, 1947 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Caudill, William A. 1947 (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - De Vos, George Alphonse, 1946-1947 (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - Gower, Charlotte Day. 1938-1947 [1990] (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - Green, Barbara, 1946-1947 (Box 120, Folder 21)
    - Hewitt, Charles M. 1944-1947 (Box 120, Folder 22)
    - Higier, Faye, 1944-1947 (Box 120, Folder 23)
    - Lessa, William Armand, 1938-1947 (Box 120, Folder 24)
    - Lesses, Milton, 1946-1947 (Box 120, Folder 25)
    - McAllister, J. Gilbert, 1933, 1939, 1947 (Box 120, Folder 26)
    - Oshinsky, Lawrence, 1943-1947 (Box 120, Folder 27)
    - Padilla, Elena I. 1945-1947 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Rowland, Ernestine, 1947 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Sears, William Hulse, 1946-1947 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Sims, Henry F.M. 1936, 1946-1947 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Watson, James Bennett, 1941-1947 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Webster, Kenneth H. 1946-1947 (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Austin, Lewis, F. 1946-1948 (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Barth, Molly Allee, 1943-1948 (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Bro, Alice K. 1944-1948 (Box 121, Folder 9)
    - Chave, Margaret E. 1946-1948 (Box 121, Folder 10)
    - Duncan, Hugh D. 1940, 1946, 1948 (Box 121, Folder 11)
    - Graham, Roy, 1948 (Box 121, Folder 12)
    - Holmes, Lionel, 1946-1948 (Box 121, Folder 13)
    - Horner, [George Roland], 1942, 1948 (Box 121, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Fleda, 1947-1948 (Box 121, Folder 15)
    - Lee, Thomas E. 1948 (Box 121, Folder 16)
    - Rotheart, George S. 1948 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Ruetz, Joseph H. 1948 (Box 121, Folder 18)
    - Steinbach, Norman, 1946-1948 (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - Woodman, Harold, 1948 (Box 121, Folder 20)
    - Bell, Robert Eugene, 1944-1949 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - Davidson, Clare, 1949 (Box 121, Folder 22)
    - Deyling, Rosemary J. 1948-1949 (Box 121, Folder 23)
    - Greenebaum, Henry E. 1949 (Box 121, Folder 24)
    - Guthe, Alfred K. 1941-1949 (Box 121, Folder 25)
    - Hanna, Herbert L. 1949 (Box 121, Folder 26)
    - Harris, Grace G. 1948-1949 (Box 121, Folder 27)
    - Holmberg, Allan, 1938, 1945-1949 (Box 121, Folder 28)
    - Jennings, Jesse David, 1935-1949 (Box 121, Folder 29)
    - Jones, Robert Roberts, 1941-1949 (Box 121, Folder 30)
    - Kelliher, Gertrude, 1948-1949 (Box 121, Folder 31)
    - Kivela, Arthur F. 1949 (Box 121, Folder 32)
    - Kraus, Bertram Shirley, 1943-1949 (Box 121, Folder 33)
    - Lehmer, Donald J. 1943-1949 (Box 121, Folder 34)
    - Maynard, Paul John, 1938-1949 (Box 121, Folder 35)
    - Merrill, Richard, 1946, 1949 (Box 121, Folder 36)
    - Miller, Walter B. 1940-1949 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - McCoullough, Richard R. 1948-1949 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - McSurely, William C. 1942, 1949 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Renne, Richard C. 1949 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Sady, Rachel Reese, 1941-1949 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Shalkp, Robert L. 1947-1949 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Sporn, Joseph, 1948-1949 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - Wagner, Mario, 1942-1943, 1949 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - Armstrong, Robert C.1939-1950 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Bennett, Wendell Clark, 1944-1950 (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Bergman, Bruce O. 1949-1950 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Bott, Elizabeth June, 1947-1950 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Brooks, Dorothy, K. 1950 (Box 122, Folder 13)
    - Daly, Marcus John. 1950 (Box 122, Folder 14)
    - Finston, Irving L. 1948-1950 (Box 122, Folder 15)
    - Fleming, Edith M. 1948-1950 (Box 122, Folder 16)
    - Gillette, Charles E. 1948-1950 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Ginsburg, Inez Mora, 1949-1950 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Hooper, James, 1950 (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Humphrey, Robert, 1949-1950 (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Jacobs, Henry E. 1949-1950 (Box 122, Folder 21)
    - Johnson, Kenneth W. 1949-1950 (Box 122, Folder 22)
    - Jones, Robert C. 1933, 1950 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Kline, Elmer Lee, 1947-1950 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Lawson, Barbara Anne, 1949-1950 (Box 122, Folder 25)
    - Levin, Mary Aline, 1950 (Box 122, Folder 26)
    - Lifschultz, Charles A. 1949-1950 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Mahoney, Frank J. 1948-1950 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Martin, Thomas Ralph, 1949-1950 (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Miles, Susannah M. 1944-1950 (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - McDonaldson, Howard, 1950 (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Nelson, Margaret W 1948-1950 (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Newmann, George Karl, 1941-1950 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Otten, Charlotte, 1944-1950 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Planalp, Jack M. 1946-1948, 1950 (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Shimbel, Constance R. [Hand-Written Addition: Mrs. Sutton], 1948-1950 (Box 123, Folder 10)
    - Singleton, John a. 1949-1950 (Box 123, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Ross Duane, 1950 (Box 123, Folder 12)
    - Snodgrass, Richard M. 1949-1950 (Box 123, Folder 13)
    - Spencer, Katherine, 1940-1950 (Box 123, Folder 14)
    - Spicer, Edward Holland, 1938-1950 [1983] (Box 123, Folder 15)
    - Stahl, Gerald M. 1949-1950 (Box 123, Folder 16)
    - Steven-Hubbard, Norman, 1948-1950 (Box 123, Folder 17)
    - Turner, Eric, 1949-1950 (Box 123, Folder 18)
    - Whiting, Alfred F. 1938-1950 (Box 123, Folder 19)
    - Zide, Norman Harbert, 1950 (Box 123, Folder 20)
    - Basehart, Harry, 1941-1951 (Box 123, Folder 21)
    - Clifton, James Alfred, 1950-1951 (Box 123, Folder 22)
    - Gregory, Hugh H, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 23)
    - Gross, Ruth Glazier, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 24)
    - Johnston, Stuart Adams, 1949-1951 (Box 123, Folder 25)
    - Khatami, Abulgasim Sayyid, 1950-1951 (Box 123, Folder 26)
    - Lang, Gottfried, 1947-1951 (Box 123, Folder 27)
    - Lewis, Sally, 1951 (Box 123, Folder 28)
    - Lieber, Dorothy Marion, 1950-1951 (Box 123, Folder 29)
    - Mahoney, Francis B. 1949-1951 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Marzano, Ruth Anne [Hand-written Addition: Lituak], 1946-1951 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Mendelson, Burton M. 1949-1951 (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Mills, Andrew, Jr. 1950-1951 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Milton, Edward, 1950-1951 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Moore, Glenna M. 1951 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Nachtrieb, Mary W. 1951 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Nichols, Herman W. 1949-1951 (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Orenstein, Henry, 1951 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Pinta, Tamara, 1949-1951 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Planalp, Shirley M. 1945-1951 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Roessel, Robert, 1948-1951 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Rowe, Chandler William, 1946-1951 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Schuman, George G. 1950-1951 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Strang, Gordon Kenneth, 1950-1951 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Sucliffe, Martha Murray, 1950-1951 (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Taylor, Herbert Cecil, 1949-1951 (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Wartenberg, Eugene Veith, 1949-1950 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Whiteford, Andrew Hunter, 1943-1951 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Wisdom, Charles W. 1930-1933, 1949-1951 [1976] (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Adams, John Boman, 1941-1952 (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Allen, Gerald C. 1952 (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - Beery, Ronald Dale, 1952 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Biddle, Peter de Haven, 1948-1952 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Bowers, William B. 1951-1952 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Bradley, Marguerite, 1950-1952 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Paula, 1949-1952 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Buitron, Anibal, 1943-1952 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Butt, Audrey J. 1950-1952 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Camara-Barbachaw, Fernando, 1950-1952 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Carterette, Teresa J. 1950-1952 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Cook, Philip Remington, 1950-1952 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Corcoran, Adrian, J. 1947-1952 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Cottrell, William Frederick, 1952 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Dahl, Patricia Ann, 1952 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Dworkin, William, 1952 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Gansberg, Joan, 1949-1952 (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Gonzales, Moreno, 1952 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Graebner, Martin L. 1948-1952 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Hagen, Richard, 1946-1952 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Jacobson, Saul Nathan, 1949-1952 (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Katzman, Ellen, 1951-1952 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Lemmon, John C. 1951-1952 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Messinger, Susan F. 1948-1952 (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Miller, Charles R. 1952 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Peck, John G. 1952 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Osanai, Iva T [Hand-written Addition: Mrs. Karl Schmitt], 1950-1952 (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Schnayer, Muriel, 1950-1952 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Sellers, Mary H. 1944-1952 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Sio, Arnold A. 1944, 1949, 1952 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Sorenson, Arthur J. 1949-1952 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Stritzel, Arlys J. 1952 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Tardits, Claude, 1951-1952 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Velez, Francisco A. 1949-1952 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - Wardlow, Margaret, 1946-1952 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - Wiesender, Carolyn, 1950-1952 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - Wolfson, Davida M. (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - Abel, Gerard Foster, 1951-1953 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Adams, Barbara M. 1949-1953 (Box 126, Folder 14)
    - Agnew, Louise F. 1946, 1953 (Box 126, Folder 15)
    - Briton, Norman. 1951-1953 (Box 126, Folder 16)
    - Brokaw, William H. 1951-1953 (Box 126, Folder 17)
    - Caldwell, Joseph R. [Folder #2], 1953 (Box 126, Folder 18)
    - Carson, William M. 1953 (Box 126, Folder 19)
    - Cunningham, Walter Eugene, 1951-1953 (Box 126, Folder 20)
    - Dyck, Linda S. 1953 (Box 126, Folder 21)
    - Emerson, John Norman, 1941-1953 (Box 126, Folder 22)
    - Foster, James. 1953 (Box 126, Folder 23)
    - Gavan, James Anderson, 1943-1953 (Box 127, Folder 1)
    - Hirsch, David I. 1948, 1951-1953 (Box 127, Folder 2)
    - Howe, Bruce, 1952-1953 (Box 127, Folder 3)
    - Hubbard, Lee L. 1951-1953 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Johnson, Leonard G. 1949-1953 (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Jones, Robert W. Jr. 1949-1953 (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Kaplan, Bernice, 1944-1953 (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Murphy, Emmett J. 1950-1953 (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - McClure, P McCombs, 1953 (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Procaccio, Guy, 1953 (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Ritter, Edith, 1952-1953 (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Scholes, Robert T. 1953 (Box 127, Folder 12)
    - Singh, Ram Raj Prasad, 1953 (Box 127, Folder 13)
    - Skinner, Mark, 1950-1953 (Box 127, Folder 14)
    - Sklow, Isobel, 1940-1953 (Box 127, Folder 15)
    - T homas, Fred L. 1953 (Box 127, Folder 16)
    - Vieth, Richard N. 1951-1953 (Box 127, Folder 17)
    - Werner, George P. 1948-1953 (Box 127, Folder 18)
    - Abrams, Sheldon Joseph, 1954 (Box 127, Folder 19)
    - Baer, Melvyn Jerome, 1936-1954 (Box 127, Folder 20)
    - Bailey, Wilfred C. 1943-1954 (Box 127, Folder 21)
    - Blaine, William McKinley Jr. 1954 (Box 127, Folder 22)
    - Bordie, John George, 1947-1954 (Box 127, Folder 23)
    - Davis, Richard H. 1954 (Box 127, Folder 24)
    - Cameron, Peter, 1953-1954 (Box 127, Folder 25)
    - Cole, Zane Allen, 1954 (Box 127, Folder 26)
    - Cohen, Herbert, 1950-1954 (Box 127, Folder 27)
    - Collier, Donald, 1938-1954 (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Drake, John Gibb St. Clair [Folder #1] (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Erickson, Charles J. 1952-1954 (Box 128, Folder 3)
    - D'Este, Jean N. 1953-1954 (Box 128, Folder 4)
    - Golden, Bernard, 1953-1954 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Golden, John S. 1949-1954 (Box 128, Folder 6)
    - Graslund, Per H. 1953-1954 (Box 128, Folder 7)
    - Hatcher, Evelyn, 1947-1954 (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - Karbel, Lois, 1954 (Box 128, Folder 9)
    - Kluckhohn, Richard P. 1951-1954 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Marlin, Joseph R. [Paper], 1954 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - Mayer-Oakes, William J. 1949-1954 (Box 128, Folder 12)
    - Mendelson, [Michel] [Addition: PhD. Thesis], 1952-1954 (Box 128, Folder 13)
    - Merz, Robert N. 1941-1954 (Box 128, Folder 14)
    - Peavy, Charles R. 1945-1954 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - Henning, P. Siverts, 1953-1954 (Box 128, Folder 16)
    - Vetter, Erika, 1953-1954 (Box 128, Folder 17)
    - Whitburn, Shirley Ann, 1952-1954 (Box 128, Folder 18)
    - White, Clay, 1954 (Box 128, Folder 19)
    - Ablin, Lois Deane, 1952-1955 (Box 128, Folder 20)
    - Adams, Robert McCormack Jr. 1943-1955 (Box 128, Folder 21)
    - Alford, Jeff, 1952-1955 (Box 128, Folder 22)
    - Allen, Rosemary, 1951-1955 (Box 128, Folder 23)
    - Ballingall, Carol Estella, 1948-1955 (Box 129, Folder 1)
    - Barker, John W., 1954-1955 (Box 129, Folder 2)
    - Dwyer, James S. 1955 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Egawa, Yoshie, 1954-1955 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Ferguson, Jack L. 1949-1955 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Florsheim, Thomas W. 1953-1955 (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - Grange, Roger Tibbetts, Jr. 1948-1955 (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - Hanna, Robert E. 1949-1955 (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - Hawkinson, John Lowell, 1954-1955 (Box 129, Folder 9)
    - Junker, Buford, 1941-1955 (Box 129, Folder 10)
    - Kennen, Janice Horstawi, 1955 (Box 129, Folder 11)
    - Liss, Allen Stanley, 1949-1955 (Box 129, Folder 12)
    - Matz, Milton, 1943-1955 (Box 129, Folder 13)
    - Metros, Janice, 1955 (Box 129, Folder 14)
    - Nash, Philleo, 1934-1937, 1955, [1987] (Box 129, Folder 15)
    - Ramsay, Carl, 1955 (Box 129, Folder 16)
    - Rapoport, Robert N. 1949-1955 (Box 129, Folder 17)
    - Ross, William T. 1953-1955 (Box 129, Folder 18)
    - Sieber, Sylvester A. 1941-1955 (Box 129, Folder 19)
    - Siegel, Bernard Joseph, 1943-1955 (Box 129, Folder 20)
    - Sims, Howard Nelson, 1948-1955 (Box 129, Folder 21)
    - Sutcliffe, John Newton, 1950-1955, [1971] (Box 129, Folder 22)
    - Vogt, Evon Zartman, 1946-1955 (Box 129, Folder 23)
    - White, Leslie A. 1940-1955 (Box 129, Folder 24)
    - Wilson, Jacqueline, 1954-1955 (Box 129, Folder 25)
    - Winchester, Harold. 1946-1955 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Abarbanel, Jay, 1956 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Alderman, Libby, 1955-1956 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Bello, Moises C. 1954-1956 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Beune, Lois Annette, 1953-1956 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Braun, Henry A. 1950-1956 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Bruner, Edward M. 1949-1956 (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Callender, Charles [Folder #2], 1956 (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Garro, J. Eugene. 1951, 1956 (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - Graham, Robert A. 1956, undated (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - Johnson, Harold B. Jr. 1955-1956 (Box 130, Folder 11)
    - Kaprelian, Renee, 1955-1956 (Box 130, Folder 12)
    - Kennen, Richard W. 1955-1956 (Box 130, Folder 13)
    - Kimura, Yoshinari, 1954-1956 (Box 130, Folder 14)
    - Kupterberg, Shirley Rubin 1954-1956 (Box 130, Folder 15)
    - Levin, Jo Anne Ely, 1954-1956 (Box 130, Folder 16)